

Anael Nachtomi

A highly motivated and proactive individual who is keen to bring previously acquired skills and experience.

I am a hard worker and would like to continue my personal and professional development.

I am a fast learner and independent person who likes to integrate into teamwork.

Contact

& 052-3914543



Anuki93@gmail.com



in Anael Nachtomi

Skills

UX/UI Design

Figma - Full Control

Adobe Creative Suite

Key Strengths

Team Collaboration

Time Management

Attention to Detail

Languages

Hebrew - Native

English - Fluent

Work Experience

OPERATION AND SECURITY OFFICER

2020 - 2023

SEA SHEPHERD I WEST AFRICA

- Managing and overseeing complex operations in the high seas
- · Providing mentorship and training on board the vessel
- Research, surveillance and detection of illegal, unreported and unregulated (IUU) fishing

OPEN WATER SCUBA INSTRUCTOR

2018 - 2023

THAILAND, ZANZIBAR, AND ISRAEL

- Conduct diving courses and manage boat operations
- Teaching and guiding groups of students both above and underwater
- · Boat safety and equipment handling

MILITARY SERVICE

2013 - 2017

COMMANDER IN THE ISRAELI MILITARY PIONEERING TRAINING PROGRAM

- Responsible for training, mentoring and welfare of the soldiers
- In command of 25+ soldiers

SPECIAL FORCES OPERATIVE | A SOLDIER IN THE UNIT

- Top secret classification
- · Intense and dynamic role
- The role required creative thinking, problem-solving skills, and adaptability

Education

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (BBA)

2023 - 2024

THE OPEN UNIVERSITY

UX/UI COURSE

2023 - 2024

NETCRAFT ACADEMY

TRAVEL GUIDE ABROAD COURSE

2023 - 2024

THE GEOGRAPHICAL COMPANY

Volunteer Experience

2012 - 2013

MANOF - A VILLAGE FOR AT-RISK YOUTH | ACCRE

- · Support, guide and work with youth with drug addiction, violent homes and criminal background.
- Living in a commune with another 15 volunteers